ringingbells.co.in 2016-06-17

# Ringing Bells | Smartphone

Ringing Bells makes all endeavours to protect the information provided to us by the users of the website. Our privacy policy follows reasonable norms to safeguard personal and sensitive information it receives from its customers and service receivers.

Our privacy policy reveals the practices/policies followed by Ringing Bell for collecting, storing, retrieving or using personal data and sensitive personal data or information it may receive from its users of the Site.

### Definitions

"Applicable Law" means all applicable statutes, acts of Indian legislature, ordinances, rules, bye-laws, regulations, notifications, circulars, guidelines, policies, directions, directives and orders of any government, statutory authority, regulatory authority, tribunal, board or court in India; " General Information"" will have the same meaning ascribed to it in clause 2.5 of the Policy. "Personal Information"" shall mean information disclosed by or obtained from any User and includes name, age, occupation, email, residential address, telephone number, payment processing details and any other personal details capable of identifying such a person. "Sensitive Personal Information" shall, excluding any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or is furnished under Applicable Laws, mean the following information:

  * account password,

  * physical, physiological or mental health condition,
  * sexual orientation; medical records and history;
  * financial information such as bank account or credit/debit card details or other payment instruction details

"User" means any Person who visits or uses the Site or avails of the services at the Site.

Those using this website might be needed to provide us with certain information on personal front regarding themselves while surfing through or availing the services of the site.

### Cash on Delivery 

This is a convenience charge that we charge you for orders of Value less than 1000 INR. This amounts to 50 INR. This charge shall be in addition to the shipping cost. Cash on Delivery is Free for all orders worth Rs.1000 and above.

### Personal Information

Before filling in any personal information, you grant a consent to Ringing Bells to use the information as it feels fit. Rest assured, we shall be using your personal and sensitive information for lawful reasons & purposes only that are related to functionality of site and only authorised personnel and associates of Ringing Bells shall have access to your personal data. In event of any legal issue, we might disclose this information to legal and Government agencies under any applicable law, without any prior notice to the user.

If we transfer your information to any third parties, working in association with Ringing Bells, we shall inform and take permission from you provided, the same level and standards of data protection are taken up by the third party. Such data transfer shall only be for lawful purposes or contracts between Ringing Bells and third parties. However, we shall not be liable for loss of confidentiality be it, direct, indirect, consequential or incidental, attributable to third parties or misuse of information or unauthorized access through factors beyond the control of Ringing Bells.

Ringing Bells shall not be responsible for accuracy & completeness of the personal/sensitive information that you provide us with or any consequences arising as a result of incomplete and/or incorrect information provided.

The personal or sensitive data that you share with us, might be used by us for creating content or recommended products relevant to you. This information also helps us maintain a database of the user accounts on our website and to evaluate as well as manage any disputes or problems that might arise with the sage of the website. 

### General information

Our servers might record certain non-sensitive and general information like: number of visits, date and time of visits, kind of browser being used and IP address of the device being used. This information derived might be used by Ringing Bells to analyses traffic patterns, statistical analysis and promotional purposes. Such general information can also be shared by us with any third party for betterment of our website, at our own discretion.

### Cookies

When a user visits and browses through our site, cookies are by default sent to the device being. These cookies can be disabled by you, if you wish to. However, turning cookies off might lead to disturbance in effective functioning of certain parts of the website. The sole purpose of sending cookies to your device is to track your preferences, browsing and ordering trends as well as improving search results and suggestions for you.

### Contact us:

### Hyperlinks to other websites

There might be links on our website that direct you to other websites or the vice versa. When you are redirected to any other website, the privacy policy of the other sites shall be applicable and our liability cases.

© Copyright Ringing Bells Pvt. Ltd. | All Rights Reserved
